

## **EDUCATION**

#### **BUSINESS STUDIES**

Major General Mahmudul Hasan Adarsh College ,Tangail 2020-2022

### **MANAGEMENT**

Govt. M M Ali College And university
Tangail
2022- Ongoing

## REFERENCE

Apurbo Debnath Manager I HOLY IT

Phone

+880 01309666788

**Email** 

akitpaul948@gmail.com

website techpartit.net

Address

Tangail,Dhaka, Bangladesh Zip Code - 1900

# AKIT KUMAR

VIDEO EDITOR

### **ABOUT ME**

Hello,

I am Akit Kumar

I am a professional Video Editing working for last 5 years as a freelancer on different freelancing platforms and head completed thousands of challenging jobs. As a professional video editing having a track record of success, I can offer you a great deal. If you need any video edit related work, just give me a message I would be happy to help.

I always try to make creative, unique & professional editing for my client

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2019-2022 GRAPHIC DESIGNER AND VIDEO EDITOR

Holy IT / Mymensingh, Bangladesh

I worked as a graphic designer and video editor Trainer at Holy IT from 2019 to 2022.

2022-Present CEO AND FOUNDER

Techpart IT / Tangail, Bangladesh

Since 2022 I have been continuously working as CEO &

Founder in our own company Techpart IT.

### SOFTWARE SKILL

Adobe Premiere Pro Adobe After Effect

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Audition